{"sid": "1RAS7GJC89TK_main", "calc_equals_delay": 5, "block_data": {"block_0": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 334065, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "300", "question_time_start": 334065, "question": "7+68+83", "correct_answer": 158, "events": [["submit", 348321]], "time_left_end": "286", "answered_time": 348321, "user_answer": "158", "user_correct": "True", "score": "1"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "286", "question_time_start": 348321, "question": "34+873", "correct_answer": 907, "events": [["calc_3", 352392], ["calc_4", 352788], ["calc_+", 353260], ["calc_8", 353663], ["calc_7", 354079], ["calc_3", 354448], ["calc_=", 354927], ["submit", 362566]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "272", "answered_time": 362566, "user_answer": "907", "user_correct": "True", "score": "2"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "272", "question_time_start": 362566, "question": "6+7+7+43", "correct_answer": 63, "events": [["submit", 369448]], "time_left_end": "265", "answered_time": 369448, "user_answer": "63", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "265", "question_time_start": 369448, "question": "24+516", "correct_answer": 540, "events": [["submit", 373934]], "time_left_end": "261", "answered_time": 373934, "user_answer": "540", "user_correct": "True", "score": "4"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "261", "question_time_start": 373934, "question": "63+13", "correct_answer": 76, "events": [["submit", 376385]], "time_left_end": "258", "answered_time": 376385, "user_answer": "76", "user_correct": "True", "score": "5"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "258", "question_time_start": 376385, "question": "78+37+23+47", "correct_answer": 185, "events": [["submit", 388864]], "time_left_end": "246", "answered_time": 388864, "user_answer": "185", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "246", "question_time_start": 388864, "question": "4+24+17", "correct_answer": 45, "events": [["submit", 393996]], "time_left_end": "241", "answered_time": 393996, "user_answer": "45", "user_correct": "True", "score": "7"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "241", "question_time_start": 393997, "question": "8+98+77", "correct_answer": 183, "events": [["submit", 402705]], "time_left_end": "232", "answered_time": 402705, "user_answer": "183", "user_correct": "True", "score": "8"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "232", "question_time_start": 402705, "question": "4+3+6+13", "correct_answer": 26, "events": [["submit", 406983]], "time_left_end": "228", "answered_time": 406983, "user_answer": "26", "user_correct": "True", "score": "9"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "228", "question_time_start": 406983, "question": "38+96", "correct_answer": 134, "events": [["submit", 415427]], "time_left_end": "219", "answered_time": 415427, "user_answer": "134", "user_correct": "True", "score": "10"}}}, "block_1": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 415427, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "219", "question_time_start": 415427, "question": "97+226", "correct_answer": 323, "events": [["submit", 425545]], "time_left_end": "209", "answered_time": 425545, "user_answer": "323", "user_correct": "True", "score": "11"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "209", "question_time_start": 425545, "question": "43+26", "correct_answer": 69, "events": [["submit", 430983]], "time_left_end": "204", "answered_time": 430983, "user_answer": "69", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "204", "question_time_start": 430983, "question": "8+84+84", "correct_answer": 176, "events": [["submit", 441351]], "time_left_end": "193", "answered_time": 441351, "user_answer": "176", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "193", "question_time_start": 441351, "question": "4+7+9+34", "correct_answer": 54, "events": [["submit", 446462]], "time_left_end": "188", "answered_time": 446462, "user_answer": "54", "user_correct": "True", "score": "14"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "188", "question_time_start": 446462, "question": "3+6+6+99", "correct_answer": 114, "events": [["submit", 451650]], "time_left_end": "183", "answered_time": 451650, "user_answer": "114", "user_correct": "True", "score": "15"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "183", "question_time_start": 451650, "question": "23+583", "correct_answer": 606, "events": [["submit", 455372]], "time_left_end": "179", "answered_time": 455372, "user_answer": "606", "user_correct": "True", "score": "16"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "179", "question_time_start": 455372, "question": "53+44+24+59", "correct_answer": 180, "events": [["submit", 474643]], "time_left_end": "160", "answered_time": 474643, "user_answer": "180", "user_correct": "True", "score": "17"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "160", "question_time_start": 474643, "question": "7+63+49", "correct_answer": 119, "events": [["submit", 480518]], "time_left_end": "154", "answered_time": 480518, "user_answer": "119", "user_correct": "True", "score": "18"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "154", "question_time_start": 480518, "question": "9+59+28", "correct_answer": 96, "events": [["submit", 487178]], "time_left_end": "147", "answered_time": 487178, "user_answer": "96", "user_correct": "True", "score": "19"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "147", "question_time_start": 487178, "question": "23+53", "correct_answer": 76, "events": [["submit", 489775]], "time_left_end": "145", "answered_time": 489775, "user_answer": "76", "user_correct": "True", "score": "20"}}}, "block_2": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 489775, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "145", "question_time_start": 489775, "question": "26+819", "correct_answer": 845, "events": [["submit", 496949]], "time_left_end": "138", "answered_time": 496949, "user_answer": "845", "user_correct": "True", "score": "21"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "138", "question_time_start": 496949, "question": "26+58+26+88", "correct_answer": 198, "events": [["submit", 508914]], "time_left_end": "126", "answered_time": 508914, "user_answer": "198", "user_correct": "True", "score": "22"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "126", "question_time_start": 508914, "question": "54+74", "correct_answer": 128, "events": [["submit", 513234]], "time_left_end": "121", "answered_time": 513234, "user_answer": "128", "user_correct": "True", "score": "23"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "121", "question_time_start": 513234, "question": "26+777", "correct_answer": 803, "events": [["submit", 521206]], "time_left_end": "113", "answered_time": 521206, "user_answer": "803", "user_correct": "True", "score": "24"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "113", "question_time_start": 521206, "question": "6+58+56", "correct_answer": 120, "events": [["submit", 530970]], "time_left_end": "104", "answered_time": 530970, "user_answer": "120", "user_correct": "True", "score": "25"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "104", "question_time_start": 530970, "question": "6+8+8+29", "correct_answer": 51, "events": [["submit", 541546]], "time_left_end": "93", "answered_time": 541546, "user_answer": "51", "user_correct": "True", "score": "26"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "93", "question_time_start": 541547, "question": "9+36+79", "correct_answer": 124, "events": [["submit", 554060]], "time_left_end": "80", "answered_time": 554060, "user_answer": "124", "user_correct": "True", "score": "27"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "80", "question_time_start": 554061, "question": "7+6+9+99", "correct_answer": 121, "events": [["submit", 570561]], "time_left_end": "64", "answered_time": 570561, "user_answer": "118", "user_correct": "False", "score": "26"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "64", "question_time_start": 570561, "question": "6+54+73", "correct_answer": 133, "events": [["submit", 576713]], "time_left_end": "58", "answered_time": 576713, "user_answer": "133", "user_correct": "True", "score": "27"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "58", "question_time_start": 576714, "question": "39+48", "correct_answer": 87, "events": [["submit", 580290]], "time_left_end": "54", "answered_time": 580290, "user_answer": "87", "user_correct": "True", "score": "28"}}}, "block_3": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 580290, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "54", "question_time_start": 580290, "question": "4+9+7+44", "correct_answer": 64, "events": [["submit", 588074]], "time_left_end": "46", "answered_time": 588074, "user_answer": "64", "user_correct": "True", "score": "29"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "46", "question_time_start": 588075, "question": "46+129", "correct_answer": 175, "events": [["submit", 596040]], "time_left_end": "39", "answered_time": 596040, "user_answer": "173", "user_correct": "False", "score": "28"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "39", "question_time_start": 596040, "question": "18+54+53+83", "correct_answer": 208, "events": [["submit", 612745]], "time_left_end": "22", "answered_time": 612745, "user_answer": "208", "user_correct": "True", "score": "29"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "22", "question_time_start": 612745, "question": "7+77+17", "correct_answer": 101, "events": [["submit", 620398]], "time_left_end": "14", "answered_time": 620398, "user_answer": "101", "user_correct": "True", "score": "30"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "14", "question_time_start": 620398, "question": "8+9+3+16", "correct_answer": 36, "events": [["submit", 624798]], "time_left_end": "10", "answered_time": 624798, "user_answer": "36", "user_correct": "True", "score": "31"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "10", "question_time_start": 624798, "question": "34+78", "correct_answer": 112, "events": [["submit", 630243]], "time_left_end": "4", "answered_time": 630243, "user_answer": "112", "user_correct": "True", "score": "32"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "4", "question_time_start": 630243, "question": "9+38+67", "correct_answer": 114, "events": []}}}}}